Guide to the Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 2
Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 2
- Box: 33, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Communication of the International Conference of the Syndicalist unions, 1920; Publication (Box 33, Folder 15)
- Box: 33, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: International Federation of Trade Unions, correspondence 8th January, 1936, Publication (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Internationale Gewerkschafts-Korrespondenz, Nummer 1, Jahrgang 2, 7 Januar 1914, Publication (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Internationale Gewerkschafts-Korrespondenz, Nummer5, Jahrgang 2, 6 Marz 1914, Publication (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: International Trade Union Women in Conference, 1927; Publication (Box 33, Folder 16)
    Author: International Federation of Trade Unions
  - Item 5: Social Legislation, 1924; Publication (Box 33, Folder 16)
    Author: Jan Oudegeest
  - Item 6: The International Federation of Trade Unions and Economic Reconstruction, 1922; Publication (Box 33, Folder 16)
    Author: Leon Jouhaux
  - Item 7: The International Federation of Trade Unions and Economic Reconstruction, 1922; Publication (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Item 8: The International Federation of Trade Unions: Its Developments and Aims, 1922; Publication (Box 33, Folder 16)
    Author: Edo Fimmen
  - Item 9: Recent Developments in Workers' Education -- The International Trade Union Movement, Volume XIX, Numbers 8-12, August-December 1939, Publication (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Item 10: The Leaders of the International Trade Union Movement in 1926, Publication (Box 33, Folder 16)
    Notes: postcards
  - Item 11: The Trade Union Movement of Great Britain, 1926; Publication (Box 33, Folder 16)
    Author: Walter M. Citrine
  - Item 12: Women and Children in the Textile Industry: An International Survey of Hours of Work and Age of Entry, 1922; Publication (Box 33, Folder 16)
    Author: Dr. Marion Phillips
  - Item 13: Working Women in Many Countries, Report of Congress, 1923; Publication (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Item 14: The Protection of Young Workers throughout the World: A Summary of the protective legislative measures for Young Workers in the various countries, 1922; Publication (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Item 15: Industrial Conditions Among Women in China, 1923; Publication (Box 33, Folder 16)
- Box: 33, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Paralelismo historico de Mexico y el Peru, 1960; Publication (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Informe sobre "Derecho de organizacion de los servidores publicos", 1960; Publication (Box 33, Folder 17)
    Author: Organizaciones de Servidores Publicos en el Hemisferio Occidental
  - Item 3: Conference of Public Service Organizations of the Western Hemisphere, 1960; Publication (Box 33, Folder 17)
    Author: International Federation of Unions of Employees in Public and Civil Services
  - Item 4: Conference of Public Service Organizations of the Western Hemisphere, Conference Delegates, Information for the use of PSI, 1960; Publication (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: Conferencia de las Organizaciones de Servidores Publicos en el Hemisferio Occidental, 1960; Publication (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: Conferencia de las Organizaciones de Servidores Publicos en el Hemisferio Occidental, 1960; Publication (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Item 7: Conferencia de las Organizaciones de Servidores Publicos en el Hemisferio Occidental, Horario de la Conferencia, 1960; Publication (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Item 8: El Roy y la Responsabilidad del Movimiento Sindical de los Servidores o Empleados Publicos en la Sociedad Moderna, Publication (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Item 9: Internacional de Servidores Publicos, Publication (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Item 10: International Conference for Water - Gas - and Electricity Workers, 1958; Publication (Box 33, Folder 17)
    Author: K. Osterkamp
  - Item 11: International Conference for Water - Gas - and Electricity Workers, 1958; Publication (Box 33, Folder 17)
    Author: R. G. Cook
  - Item 12: International Conference for Water - Gas - and Electricity Workers, 1958; Publication (Box 33, Folder 17)
    Author: Elvin Andersson
  - Item 13: International Conference for Water - Gas and Electricity Workers, 1958; Publication (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Item 14: International Labour Conference: Convention (No. 87) Concerning Freedom of Association and Protection of the Right to Organise, Publication (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Item 15: Invitation, Agenda and Program of Festivities of the Conference of Public Service Organizations of the Western Hemisphere, to be held in Mexico City from February 8 through 12, 1960, Publication (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Item 16: La Conferencia Contara con Cuatro Comisiones de Trabajo, Ademas de la Comision de Credenciales, Publication (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Item 17: Saludo de Alfonso Sanchez Madariaga, Secretario-General de la ORIT, 1960; Publication (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Item 18: Secretaria de Estado en los Despachos de Trabajo y Prevision Social, Publication (Box 33, Folder 17)
    Author: Oscar A. Flores
  - Item 19: The P.S.I. in Italy, 1959; Publication (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Item 20: Modern Civil Service and the Position of Public Servants in Regard to Dominant Political Parties in the Government and Pressure Groups, Publication (Box 33, Folder 17)
- Box: 34, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Information Bulletin of the International Working Men's Association No.1, January 1923 - Resolutions Adopted by the International Congress of Revolutionary Syndicalists held in Berlin, Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Memoire sur la Socialisation des Moyens de Production, 1920; Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Press Reports, 1924; Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Author: John W. Brown
    Notes: Vol. II, No. 11, November 1924: International Educational Notes
  - Item 4: Press Reports, 1926; Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. III, No. 1, January 1926: International Educational Notes
  - Item 5: Press Reports, 1925; Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. III, No. 1, January, 1925
  - Item 6: Press Reports, 1925; Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. III, No. 10, October, 1925: International Educational Notes
  - Item 7: Press Reports, 1925; Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. III, No. 12, December, 1925: International Educational Notes
  - Item 8: Press Reports, 1925; Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. III, No. 2, February 1925: International Educational Notes
  - Item 9: Press Reports, 1925; Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. III, No. 3, March, 1925
  - Item 10: Press Reports, 1925; Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. III, No. 5, May, 1925
  - Item 11: Press Reports, 1925; Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. III, No. 6, June, 1925: International Educational Notes
  - Item 12: Press Reports, 1925; Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. III, No. 7, July 1925: International Educational Notes
  - Item 13: Press Reports, 1925; Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. III, No. 9, September, 1925: International Educational Notes
  - Item 14: Press Reports, 1926; Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. IV, No. 2, February 1926: International Educational Notes
  - Item 15: Press Reports, 1926; Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Notes: Vol. IV, No. 6, June 1926: International Educational Notes
  - Item 16: South African Boycott, Publication (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Box: 34, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Report of the Special Conference on Trade Union and Collective Bargaining Rights of Public Employees, 1953; Publication (Box 34, Folder 2)
    Author: Public Services International
  - Item 2: Report of the International Conference of Health Service Workers, 1956; Publication (Box 34, Folder 2)
    Author: International Conference Of Health Service Workers
- Box: 34, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Fourth General Conference: Address of the President, Ernest Green, 1956; Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
    Author: International Federation of Workers Educational Associations
  - Item 2: Fourth General Conference: Report of the Secretariat and Executive Committee for the Years 1953-1956, Publication (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Box: 34, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: International Institute for Labour Studies, 1966; Publication (Box 34, Folder 4)
    Author: International Institute for Labour Studies
  - Item 2: International Institute for Labour Studies, 1966; Publication (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: International Institute for Labour Studies, 1966; Publication (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: International Institute for Labour Studies, 1966; Publication (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Box: 34, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: International Centre for Advanced Technical and Vocational Training, Turin, Technical Information Note (No. 2), 1964; Publication (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Provisional Record, Thirty-Fifth Session, Geneva, No. 2: Appendices, 1952; Publication (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: ILO Information, 1976; Publication (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Box: 34, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Report to the Central Committee - General Electric Workers' World Coordination, 1969; Publication (Box 34, Folder 6)
    Author: International Metalworkers Federation
- Box: 34, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Rules: Purposes and Aims of the IMF, 1964; Publication (Box 34, Folder 7)
    Author: International Metalworkers' Federation
  - Item 2: Documents of the IMF Regional Conference on Metalworkers Problems in Latin America and the Caribbean, 1967; Publication (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Metal Vol. VI, Diciembre 1965-Enero/Febrero 1966, Publication (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: The Largest Steel Companies in the Free World -- Iron and Steel Department, Steelworkers' Conference, 1959; Publication (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: News in Brief: Table of Contents for 1965, Publication (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Metal, 1966; Publication (Box 34, Folder 7)
    Notes: Vol. VI, December 1965 - January/February 1966
  - Item 7: Metal, 1966; Publication (Box 34, Folder 7)
    Notes: Vol. VI, March-April 1966
  - Item 8: Metal, 1966; Publication (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: Metal, 1966; Publication (Box 34, Folder 7)
    Notes: Vol. VI, May-June 1966
- Box: 34, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: General Report IV: Summary of the Trade Union Situation and the Contractual Systems in 1968 (Up-dating of Frankfurt Document III of 1964): Automotive Section, Publication (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: The Largest Steel Companies in the Free World -- Iron and Steel Department, Steelworkers Conference, 1959; Publication (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: International Companies in the Metal Industries and Technolocial Gaps: Trade Union Advisory Committee to the OECD, Seminar on the Trade Unions and the Technological Gaps 18th-20th, September 1968: Discussion Paper No. 2 -, Publication (Box 34, Folder 8)
    Author: Karl Casserini
- Box: 34, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: General Conference of the International Trade Secretariats, 1963; Publication (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: ITS Liaison Office in Geneva Newsletter for the ITS, April-May 1961, No. 36, Publication (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: ITS Liaison Office in Geneva Newsletter for the ITS, April-May, No. 29, 1960; Publication (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: ITS Liaison Office in Geneva Newsletter for the ITS, August 1960, No. 31, Publication (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: ITS Liaison Office in Geneva Newsletter for the ITS, February-March 1961, No. 35, Publication (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: ITS Liaison Office in Geneva Newsletter for the ITS, January 1961, No. 34, Publication (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: ITS Liaison Office in Geneva Newsletter for the ITS, June-July 1960, No. 30, Publication (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: Its Liaison Office in Geneva Newsletter for the ITS, November-December 1960, No. 33, Publication (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: ITS Liaison Office in Geneva Newsletter for the ITS, September-October 1960, No. 32, Publication (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Item 10: Index of items which appeared in the Newsletter for the ITS from Spetember 1959 to October 1960 - ITS Activities, Publication (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Item 11: ITS Liason Office in Geneva Newsletter for the ITS, June-July 1961, No. 37, Publication (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Box: 34, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: General Conference of the International Trade Secretariats -- Agenda Item 8, 1959; Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Auto Unions Confer From 11 Countries, 1960; Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Correspondence - December 1960 (William C. Doherty and Velasco Ibarra), Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Curran Supports Chiding of Union: Transport Group is Backed by NMU Chief on Plan to Discipline Seafarers, 1961; Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Description of Past ITS-ICFTU Relations, 1965; Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Extraordinary General Conference of the ITS - Replies to the Circular Letter ITS/4, Addressed to the International Trade Secretariat by the ICFTU, 1959; Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Extraordinary General Conference of the ITS: Agenda, 1959; Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: Extraordinary General Conference of the ITS: Agenda Item 1, 1959; Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: Extraordinary General Conference of the ITS: Agenda Item 2, 1959; Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: Extraordinary General Conference of the ITS: Agenda Item 3, 1959; Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Item 11: General Conference of the International Trade Secretariasts, Agenda Item 10d: Situation in Cuba and International Affiliation of Cuban Trade Union, 1959; Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Item 12: General Conference of the International Trade Secretariat: List of Meetings, 1959; Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Item 13: General Conference of the International Trade Secretariats, 1963; Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Item 14: General Conference of the International Trade Secretariats, 1962; Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Item 15: General Conference of the International Trade Secretariats, Agenda Item 3: Report of the ITS Liason Officer, 1963-1964, Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Item 16: General Conference of the International Trade Secretariats: Agenda Item 10, 1959; Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Item 17: General Conference of the International Trade Secretariats: Agenda Item 10, 1959; Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Item 18: General Conference of the International Trade Secretariats: Agenda Item 4, 1959; Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Item 19: General Conference of the International Trade Secretariats: Agenda Item 5, 1959; Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Item 20: General Conference of the International Trade Secretariats: Agenda Item 6, 1959; Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Item 21: General Conference of the ITS - Joint ICFTU/ITS Consultative Committee on Women Workers' Questions: Recommendations, 1959; Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Item 22: ICFTU, Information Bulletin, Vol. XI, February 15, 1960, No. 4, pp. 19-20: News of the International Trade Secretariats - Joint ITF/ICFTU meeting on regional activities, Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Item 23: ITS Conference on Regional Activities, 1962; Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Item 24: ITS Liason Office in Geneva Newsletter for the ITS, August-September 1961, No. 38, Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Item 25: ITS Liason Office in Geneva Newsletter for the ITS, October-December 1961, No. 39, Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Item 26: ITS Liason Office in Geneva, Circular Letter No. 9/64, 1964; Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
    Author: B. Zofka
  - Item 27: Joint ICFTU/ITS Meeting on Trade Union Situations in Various Countries, 1962; Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Item 28: Report on the Extraordinary General Conference of the International Trade Secretariats -- Liason Office of the International Trade Secretariats, 1959; Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Item 29: List of ITS Addresses 1964, Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Item 30: Report on the Second ITS Conference on Regional Activities, 1963; Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Item 31: Report on: Joint ICFTU/ITS Meeting on the Trade Union Situation in Various Countries, 1963; Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Item 32: Transport Workers Assail Suez Curbs, 1960; Publication (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Box: 34, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Boletin de Noticias, 1963; Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
    Author: International Transport Workers Federation
    Notes: Ano II, N. 43, 1 de mayo de 1963
  - Item 2: Boletin de Noticias, 1965; Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
    Notes: Ano III - No. 81, 15 de Enero de 1965
  - Item 3: Boletin de Noticias, 1963; Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Boletin de Noticias, 1965; Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: 21. International Transportworkers-Congress, 21.-29. Juli 1950 Stuttgart, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: 21st Congress of the International Transport Workers Federation, Stuttgart, 21 to 29 July 1950: Resolution on ERP and OEEC, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: 21st Congress, Stuttgart, 21 to 29 July 1950, Report on Item 8 of the Agenda: Draft Resolution justifying the exclusion of the Canadian Seamen's Union, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: 21st Congress, Stuttgart, 21 to 29 July 1950, Report on the Conference of the Dockers Section, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 9: 21st Congress, Stuttgart, 21 to 29 July 1950, Resolution on the German Federal Railways, submitted by H. Jahn, German Railwaymen's Union, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
    Author: H. Jahn
  - Item 10: 21st Congress, Stuttgart, 21 to 29 July 1950: Report of the Civil Aviation Section, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 11: 21st Congress, Stuttgart, 21 to 29 July 1950: Report of the Conference of the Inland Waterway Workers Section, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 12: 21st Congress, Stuttgart, 21 to 29 July 1950: Report of the Road Transport Section, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 13: Boletin de Noticias, 1963; Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
    Notes: Ano II, N. 40, 15 de marzo de 1963
  - Item 14: Boletin de Noticias, 1965; Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 15: Boletin de Noticias, 1965; Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
    Notes: Ano III - No. 82, 1 de Febrero de 1965
  - Item 16: Boletin de Noticias, 1965; Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
    Notes: Ano III - No. 83, 15 de Febrero de 1965
  - Item 17: Boletin de Noticias, 1965; Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
    Notes: Ano III - No. 84, 15 de Marzo de 1965
  - Item 18: Boletin de Noticias, 1965; Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 19: Boletin de Noticias, 1965; Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
    Notes: Ano III - No. 86, 15 de Abril de 1965
  - Item 20: Boletin de Noticias, 1965; Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
    Notes: Ano III - No. 88, 1 de Junio de 1965
  - Item 21: Boletin de Noticias, 1965; Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 22: Boletin de Noticias, 1966; Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
    Notes: Ano IV - No. 95, 1 de Febrero de 1966
  - Item 23: Boletin de Noticias, 1963; Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
    Notes: No. 41, April 1st, 1963
  - Item 24: Boletin de Noticias, 1963; Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
    Notes: No. 44, Mat 15, 1963
  - Item 25: Boletin de Noticias, 1963; Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
    Notes: No. 44, May 15, 1963
  - Item 26: Boletin de Noticias, 1963; Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
    Notes: No. 45, June 1, 1963
  - Item 27: Boletin de Noticias, 1963; Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 28: Boletin de Noticias, 1963; Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
    Notes: No. 46, July 1, 1963
  - Item 29: Boletin de Noticias, 1963; Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 30: Boletin de Noticias, 1963; Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
    Notes: No. 47, July 15, 1963
  - Item 31: Boletin de Noticias, 1963; Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 32: Boletin de Noticias, 1963; Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
    Notes: No. 48, August 1, 1963
  - Item 33: Constitution of the International Transport Workers Federation, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 34: Correspondence - Biennial Convention of the ITF, 1950; Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
    Author: F. Strauss
  - Item 35: Negotiating Machinery on Railways in Different Countries: Northern Ireland, 1949; Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 36: Negotiating Machinery on Railways in Different Countries: Northern Ireland, 1949; Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 37: News About the ITF, No. 23, 24 November 1966, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 38: Proceeding of the Biennial Congress (21st), 1950; Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 39: Proposed International Regulations and Conventions, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 40: Report of American Committee of the International Transportworkers Federation RE: Four-day demonstration against Panlibhonco vessels in US ports, December 1-4, 1958, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 41: Resolutions adopted by the London Congress: ITS Constitution, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 42: Sixth Session, Friday, 28 July, 1950, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 43: The International Transportworkers' Federation: Its Character, its Aims, its Aspirations, 1922; Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
    Author: N. Nathans
  - Item 44: Third Session, Monday, 24 July, 1950: Continuation of discussion on the Report on Activities, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 45: Boletin de Noticias, Ano III - No. 86, 15 de Abril de 1965, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 46: Boletin de Noticias, Ano IV - No. 96, 1 de Marzo de 1966, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 47: A brief survey of the history and activities of the International Transport Workers Federation -- ITF, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
    Author: O. Becu
  - Item 48: Transporte, Ano IX, Enero-Febrero 1965, Num. 1, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 49: Transporte, Ano IX, Marzo-Abril 1965, Num. 2, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Item 50: A brief survey of the history and activities of the International Transport Workers Federation -- ITF, Publication (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Box: 34, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Boletin de Noticias, 1963; Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
    Notes: Ano II, No. 41, 1 de abril de 1963
  - Item 2: ITF Boletin de Noticias, 1963; Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: ITF Boletin de Noticias, 1963; Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Boletin de Noticias, 1963; Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: ITF Boletin de Noticias, 1963; Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: ITF Boletin de Noticias, 1963; Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 7: 21st Congress, Stuttgart, 21 to 29 July 1950: Addendum to the Report on the Conference of the Seafarers Section, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 8: 21st Congress, Stuttgart, 21 to 29 July 1950: Addendum to the Report on the Conference of the Seafarers' Section, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 9: 21st Congress, Stuttgart, 21 to 29 July 1950: General Council, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 10: Boletin de Noticias, Ano II, No. 40, 15 de marco de 1963, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Item 11: Boletin de Noticias, Ano II, No. 46, 1 de julio de 1963, Publication (Box 34, Folder 12)